## BHESH BAHADUR CHAUHAN

### Office Secretory

**☎**: 9815037488, **☎**: mretup@gmail.com

**Q**: Sukedhara- Kapan, Kathmandu, Bagmati.

#### D.O.B: 11/20/2001

Gender: Male

Marital Status: Single

Nationality: Nepal

#### **SUMMARY**

I have worked as a Teacher a facilitator, which has helped me to develop a professional attitude & enthusiasm which is helping me in pursing the field of my interest. I am passionate and highly motivated towards Information Technology and wants to build a sound career.

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

#### Office Secratory - Future Employment Service

Kathmandu, Bagmati

December 2021 - Till Date

Answering and directing the phone calls.

Organizing and distributing messages.

Maintaining company schedules.

Organizing documents and files.

Scheduling meeting and conferences.

Record keeping and maintaining the database timely.

Follow-ups and relaying the updates.

#### Computer Teacher - Swastik Pathshala

Mirchaiya, Madhesh

August 2019 - June 2020

- Planning lessons and activities that facilitate students' acquisition of basic and advanced computer skills.
- Instructing in a manner that develops students' confidence in their abilities.
- Observing and managing classroom dynamics.
- Invigilating and grading projects, quizzes, and examinations.

Computer Teacher - Ashadeep Boarding School

- Planning and Preparing the lesson.
- Encouraging student participation.
- Research and developing new teaching materials.
- Research and implementing new teaching methods.
- Marking student's work and recording performance.
- Setting assessment test and overseeing examinations.

#### **EDUCATION**

Himalayan Secondary School - High School Diploma

(Computer Enineering)

Damak, Koshi. April 2017 - May 2019

Amar Secondary School - Senior Secondary School Certificate (SSCE)

(Secondary Education)

Ilam, Koshi. May 2015 - May 2017

Mahendra Ratna Campus - Bachelor Of Engineering

(Information And Commuication Technology)

Kathmandu, Bagmati. May 2021 - Till Date

# Communication Data Operating Computer Programming Interpersonal Image Annotation

#### **HOBBIES**

Computer Programming, System & Data Analysis, Website Developing, Database Handling With SQL, Image Annotation, Graphic Design,

#### **REFEREES**

Available on Request